Class of 1938 Records, 1934-2004
Smith College Archives
Class of 1938 Records
1934-2004
Smith College. Class of 1938.
RG 80
8 boxes (5.6 linear ft.)
Smith College Archives Northampton, MA
This collection contains photographs, invitations, songs, newspaper clippings, and other memorabilia from the commencement and reunions of the Class of 1938.
Historical Note
The Class of 1938 was the sixtieth graduating class of Smith College.
Scope and Contents of the Collection
The Class of 1938 Records contain materials describing the history and activities of the Class of 1938, including materials from commencement, reunions, senior dramatics, and other important events. Types of materials include photographs, invitations, songs, newspaper clippings, questionnaires, letters, and other memorabilia.
Individual biographical files are also available, and often include photographs, photo albums, newspaper clippings, letters and correspondences, and class notes.
Information on Use
Terms of Access and Use
The records are open for research according to the regulations of the Smith College Archives without any additional restrictions.
History of the Collection
The Class of 1938 Records were created by the students and donated to the College Archives.
- Baccalaureate 1938 (Box 2109, Folder 1)
- Commencement 1938 (Box 2109, Folder 2)
- Commencement Dramatics 1938 (Box 2109, Folder 3)
- Commencement Dramatics-Photographs 1938 (Box 2109, Folder 4)
- Commencement Music 1938 (Box 2109, Folder 5)
- Commencement Photographs 1938 (Box 2109, Folder 6)
- Commencement Speaker 1938 (Box 2109, Folder 7)
- Freshman Handbook 1934-1935 (Box 2109, Folder 8)
- Fund Letters 1988-1991 (Box 2109, Folder 9)
- Smith Girls' Guidebook 1937-38 (Box 2109, Folder 9a)
- Groups 1934-1938 (Box 2109, Folder 10)
- History 1937, n.d. (Box 2109, Folder 11)
- Hoop Rolling 1938 (Box 2109, Folder 12)
- Ivy Day 1938 (Box 2109, Folder 13)
- Ivy Day-Photographs 1938 (Box 2109, Folder 14)
- Junior Prom 1937 (Box 2109, Folder 15)
- Junior Ushers 1937 (Box 2109, Folder 16)
- Last Chapel 1938 (Box 2109, Folder 17)
- Class Letters 1957-2004 (Box 2109, Folder 18)
- Class Officers 1935-1938, 1958 (Box 2109, Folder 19)
- Class Officers' Meetings-Minutes 1979-1993 (Box 2109, Folder 20)
- Rally Day 1938 (Box 2109, Folder 21)
- Reunions 1953 (Box 2109, Folder 22)
- Reunions 1958 (Box 2109, Folder 23)
- Reunions 1963 (Box 2109, Folder 24)
- Reunions 1968 (Box 2109, Folder 25)
- Reunions 1978 (Box 2109.1, Folder 1)
- Reunions 1983 (Box 2109.1, Folder 2)
- Reunions 1988 (Box 2109.1, Folder 3)
- Reunions 1993 (Box 2109.1, Folder 4)
- Senior Dramatics 1938 (Box 2109.1, Folder 5)
- Senior Prom 1938 (Box 2109.1, Folder 6)
- Senior Questionnaire 1938 (Box 2109.1, Folder 7)
- Songs n.d. (Box 2109.1, Folder 8)
- Sophomore Carnival 1936 (Box 2109.1, Folder 9)
- Sophomore Push Committee 1936 (Box 2109.1, Folder 10)
- Step Sings 1938 (Box 2109.1, Folder 11)
- Class Supper 1938 (Box 2109.1, Folder 12)
- Year Book 1938 (Box 2109.1, Folder 13)